https://www.canadianwellness.com/terms-and-conditions/

Terms and Conditions
Home Terms and Conditions
Terms and Conditions for Listing in the Canadian Wellness Directory and Privacy Policy
PLEASE READ ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND OUR PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY.
This Terms of Use and Listing Agreement (this Agreement) states the terms and conditions under which you may access and use The Canadian Wellness Directory’s (the Directory) Website.
By accessing and using any this website and/or its services, you are indicating your acceptance to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Agreement. If you do not accept these terms and conditions, you must not access or use The Canadian Wellness Directory.
Changes to the Terms and Conditions
From time to time, The Canadian Wellness Directory may change, remove, add to (including without limitation by way of Additional Terms) or modify the Terms and Privacy Policy, and reserves the right to do so in its discretion. We encourage you to periodically review the terms for listing with us and web site usage. Your continued use of any Website or Service after new and/or revised Terms indicate that you have read, understood and agreed to those Terms.
Responsibility for Content
You understand that all material, data and information, such as data files, written text, photographs, videos or other images (collectively referred to as the “Content”) which you may have access to as part of, or through your use of  are the sole responsibility of the person from which such Content originated.
You acknowledge that The Canadian Wellness Directory does not make any representations or warranties about the Content, including without limitation, about the accuracy, quality of the Content made available by users of the website.
While we review the submission and edits for accuracy and appropriateness, you understand and accept that by using this website, you may be exposed to Content that is offensive, indecent or objectionable. Under no circumstances is The Canadian Wellness Directory liable in any way for any Content, including, but not limited to: any infringing Content, any errors or omissions in Content, or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Content posted, linked to, transmitted to, or otherwise accessible or made available via the website.
Content You Provide to The Canadian Wellness Directory
You may only submit Content to the directory that you have the right to submit. This means that you can only submit Content that you have created yourself or that you have been expressly granted the right to submit and is consistent with the Terms of use and submission.
Content that infringes the rights of any third party (For instance, content used without express permission of the copyright owner) must not be submitted to the Directory. You represent, warrant and fully agree that no Content of any kind submitted, added, posted or otherwise shared by you, violates or infringes upon the rights of any third party, including copyright, privacy, trademark or proprietary rights. In addition, the content must not contain libelous, defamatory or otherwise unlawful material. No pornographic or sexually suggestive material is permitted in the directory.
Listing in the The Canadian Wellness Directory
We reserve the right to only list the business we approve. This means that event if you pay for a listing, it may not be added or listed in the directory. Listings must be based on Canada and be approved by our editorial team to get listed.
The plans listed on the page and the features within them are subject to change without notice. If the offering changes within a subscription period, you will be automatically converted to the new plan respectively or will default to the free plan if you fail to renew upon expiry.
The Canadian Wellness Directory may, but is not obligated to, review the free submissions and may delete or remove (without notice) any Content in its sole discretion that the Directory determines violates the Terms or that may be offensive, illegal, or that might violate the rights of others.
You acknowledge and agree you are solely responsible for creating backup copies and replacing any Content you post on the Directory.  You may request the removal of your Content from the Directory at any time, and The Canadian Wellness Directory will take reasonable steps to remove such Content.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY THE APPLICABLE LAW, THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY OFFERS THE DIRECTORY AS-IS AND MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND CONCERNING THE DIRECTORY, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTIBILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON INFRINGEMENT.
THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE FUNCTIONS OR CONTENT CONTAINED IN THE WEBSITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY’S SERVERS ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATION REGARDING USE OR THE RESULT OF USE OF THE CONTENT IN TERMS OF ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE USEFULNESS OF THE CONTENT.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.
EXCEPT TO THE EXTENT REQUIRED BY APPLICABLE LAW AND THEN ONLY TO THAT EXTENT, IN NO EVENT WILL THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY, ITS EMPLOYEES, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, OWNERS, INVESTORS, AFFILIATES OR AGENTS (“THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY PARTIES”) BE LIABLE TO YOU ON ANY LEGAL THEORY FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, ACTUAL, PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY OR OTHER DAMAGES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOSS OF REVENUE OR INCOME, LOST PROFITS, PAIN AND SUFFERING, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, COST AND REMOVAL OF LISTING, OR ANY OTHER DAMAGES SUFFERED OR INCURRED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY THAT ARISE IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, LISTINGS, CONTENT IN THE WEBSITE (OR THE TERMINATION OF A LISTING OR REMOVAL OF CONTENT FOR ANY REASON), EVEN IF THE THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY PARTIES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
WE ENDEAVOR TO MAINTAIN A SAFE PLACE FOR CANADIANS TO FIND FITNESS, WELLNESS, HEALTH  AND HAPPINESS SOLUTIONS. THE CANADIAN WELLNESS DIRECTORY PARTIES SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE WHATSOEVER IN ANY MANNER FOR ANY CONTENT POSTED ON THE WEBSITE (INCLUDING CLAIMS OF INFRINGEMENT RELATING TO CONTENT POSTED ON THE WEBSITES OR SERVICES, FOR THE CONDUCT OF THIRD PARTIES WHETHER ON THE WEBSITES, OR  FOR YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITES AND SERVICES IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICES OR OTHERWISE RELATING TO THE DIRECTORY AND WEBSITE.
Indemnification for Breach of Terms of Use.
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless the The Canadian Wellness Directory Parties from and against any and all loss, expenses, damages, and costs, including without limitation reasonable attorneys fees, resulting, whether directly or indirectly, from your violation of the Terms for use of this website. You also agree to indemnify and hold harmless the The Canadian Wellness Directory Parties from and against any and all claims brought by third parties arising out of your use of any of the Websites or Services and the Content you make available in the Directory by any means, including without limitation through a posting, a link, reference to Content, or otherwise.
In the event that we receive a complaint about content added to the Directory that violates the terms of use, it will be promptly removed without notice to the user who added it.
Privacy Policy
We deeply respect the privacy of all our website visitors, and any information we collect will only be used to help us operate the Directory.
When you join the Directory, you provide personal information to create an account and establish a password and both personal and business profile. We use that personal information to set-up and maintain your account and for the purpose of contacting you about leads and other communication relevant to your business listing and the Directory.
Our web server automatically collects standard information: IP addresses, referring pages, and pages visited as well. It does not collect your email address unless you provide it as part of your business or personal profile. This information is then only used internally to help us better target our website and to meet your needs.
We WILL NEVER SELL, RENT OR SHARE our  user’s list knowingly with any other business party for any reason.
The Canadian Wellness Directory reserves the right to alter this Privacy Policy at any time.
We welcome your feedback on this privacy policy, and are happy to answer any questions you have. We can be reached by e-mail or telephone.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics and Data Storage
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
